next we'll examine the brush categories
接下来 我们将检查画笔类别
in more detail located on the left is
更详细的是位于左侧的
the brush presets panel as we learned in
笔刷预设面板 如我们在中了解的
the previous lesson these tools allow us
上一课这些工具让我们
to paint on the canvas the brush presets
在画布上绘制笔刷预设
contain all the different types of media
包含所有不同类型的介质
such as markers oils and acrylics
例如记号笔油和丙烯酸
pencils and pastels by default there is
默认情况下 有铅笔和粉笔
one huge list of brushes but you can
一大堆画笔 但你可以
filter the results to show specific
过滤结果以显示特定的
categories like paint or ink you can
像油漆或墨水这样的类别你可以
adjust the icon size if you want to fit
如果想要适合 请调整图标大小
more or less brushes on the screen
屏幕上或多或少有画笔
there are also brush bundles that you
还有一些刷子束 您可以
can enable and disable to show more or
可以启用和禁用以显示更多内容或
less
较少
brushes let's try painting with a brush
画笔让我们试着用画笔作画
in the paint grouping called wet
在名为湿的油漆组中
bristles let's pick a pink color and
刷毛 让我们选一种粉色
then make a heavy to light stroke with
然后用重到轻的笔划
this brush if we compare that to another
如果我们把这把刷子和另一把比较一下
variant of the paint brush that's in the
中的画笔的变体
same category like bristles 3 large
同品类如毛茸茸3大
smooth then you can see the stroke looks
流畅 然后你就可以看到笔触看起来
a lot different the first variant has a
与第一个变种有很大不同的是
rounder dab with more oiliness and
更油腻、更圆润的轻拍
bristle definition whereas the other
刷毛定义 而另一个
brush is much
刷子多了
flatter within this grouping of paint
在这组油漆中更加平淡
brushes there are also a variety of
刷子也有各种各样的
brush
刷子
Technologies for example I have basic
例如 我有基本的技术
brushes wet brushes and even some
刷子 湿刷子 甚至一些
texture brushes depending on how you use
纹理画笔取决于您使用的方式
them the brushes in this category can be
这一类别的画笔可以是
used to create an oil acrylic or
用来制造一种油性丙烯酸或
watercolor look there are even some
水彩画看起来甚至还有一些
brushes that are strictly blenders
严格来说是搅拌器的刷子
because how you might use each brush is
因为您可以如何使用每个画笔
fairly subjective the looks you can get
你能得到的眼神相当主观
from a brush might be a lot different
从刷子上看可能会有很大的不同
than what's shown in the brush ey on I
比我的画笔上所显示的要多
encourage you to select some of these
鼓励您选择其中的一些
brushes and try them out on the canvas
画笔 然后在画布上试一试
to see what they can do keep in mind
要看看他们能做些什么 请记住
that when working digitally the brush
当以数字方式工作时 画笔
you select is not a literal
您选择的不是文字
representation of the medium it emulates
它所模拟的媒体的表示
but rather a tool that gives the effect
而是一种产生效果的工具
of that Medium if I select the sketch
如果我选择素描
chalk soft variant this is not an actual
粉笔软变体这不是实际的
stick of chalk that adds a powdery
粉笔加粉末状的粉笔
substance to the canvas it's just a
画布上的实体这只是一个
brush that resembles the look and feel
与外观和手感相似的画笔
of chalk calling this chalk is just a
粉笔叫这个粉笔只是一种
way to describe the properties of the
的属性的描述方式
brush think of the brush names and
画笔想想画笔的名字和
categories as a suggestion not a
分类作为建议 而不是
limitation on what you can create
限制您可以创建的内容
traditional rules don't apply in this
传统的规则不适用于此
space so feel free to draw with paint on
空间 所以你可以自由地画画
top of chalk or use watercolor over that
在粉笔上面或在上面用水彩
because you're a painting digitally you
因为你是一幅数字画作
can mix media together as much as you
可以像您一样将媒体混合在一起
like you can also change the look of the
例如 您还可以更改
paint on your canvas simply by blending
只需混合即可在画布上作画
it for instance you can use an oily or
例如 您可以使用油性或
wet blender on a dry medium to make it
干介质上的湿搅拌器来制作它
look wet nothing is in stone and there
看 湿淋淋的 没有什么是坚不可摧的
are very few limitations on how you can
几乎没有限制您如何
combine media from different categories
组合不同类别的媒体
together therefore I encourage you to
因此 我鼓励你们一起
use brushes from multiple categories in
使用来自多个类别的画笔
your paintings just as well don't feel
你的画也不会觉得
restricted by the traditional mediums
受传统媒体的制约
like watercolor oil or acrylic instead
像是水彩油或亚克力
just explore the brushes that interest
只需探索感兴趣的画笔
you and use them to create your own
并使用它们来创建您自己的
unique painting while it's okay to aim
别具一格的画作 瞄准也可以
for a specific mediums aesthetic it's
对于特定的媒介审美来说 它是
more important to choose the right tool
更重要的是选择正确的工具
for the job whether it's a brush for
为了这份工作 无论是为了
creating leaves on trees or a pallet
在树上或托盘上创建树叶
knife for distant water experiment with
远距离水上实验用刀
different brushes to find what works
使用不同的画笔找出有效的画笔
best for your needs you can even
最适合您的需求 您甚至可以
customize and save your own brushes and
自定义并保存您自己的画笔和
categorize them in a way that makes
对它们进行分类的方式可以使
sense to you before you go any further I
在你走得更远之前对你有意义
suggest dedicating some time to
建议将一些时间花在
exploring and experimenting with the
探索和试验
brushes and Crea to get a sense of the
刷子和Crea 以了解
different effects you can achieve don't
你能达到的不同效果不要
put pressure on yourself to create
给自己施加压力去创造
finished artwork just have fun and play
完成的艺术品只需玩乐和玩耍
around with the brushes you may want to
带着刷子 你可能会想
move the tool options out of the way so
将工具选项移到一边 以便
you can expand the brush presets to see
您可以展开笔刷预设以查看
more of the brushes at once you can also
一次使用更多的画笔也可以
keep track of your last used brushes in
记录你最近用过的刷子
the brush preset history panel to better
笔刷预置历史记录面板以更好地
understand how to work with brushes and
了解如何使用画笔和
CR let's explore the anatomy of a brush
让我们来探索一下刷子的解剖结构
each brush icon shows a preview of the
每个画笔图标都显示了
shape of the brush and some of its
画笔的形状及其一些
properties let's get a better view of
属性 让我们更好地了解
how this soft chalk brush was made by
这支柔软的粉笔是如何由
opening the brush editor from the
从打开画笔编辑器
properties bar and looking under General
属性栏并在常规下查看
brush tip here we can see the dab or the
画笔笔尖在这里 我们可以看到涂抹或
tip of the the brush as well as a sample
画笔尖端以及样品
stroke when adjusting the properties you
调整属性时的描边
can watch the stroke preview to see how
可以观看笔划预览以了解如何
each property affects a stroke this
每个属性都会影响此笔划
preview doesn't show everything a brush
预览不会显示所有内容都是画笔
can do so it can also be helpful to make
可以这样做 它也可以帮助使
Strokes on the canvas to get a feel for
画布上的笔触 以获得感觉
all of the properties of a brush the
画笔的所有属性都是
brushes and Crea and most art
画笔、油画和大多数艺术
applications work by repeating a dab
应用程序通过重复轻拍来工作
along a stroke path a dab is a
沿着笔划路径 轻拍是一个
pixel-based stamp that represents the
基于像素的图章 表示
shape of the tip of your brush or tool
画笔或工具尖端的形状
in traditional art terms the tips of a
在传统艺术术语中 一种
bristle brush would be a dab if I change
如果我换了 刷毛会是个不错的选择
to a different dab you can see the
到不同的轻拍 您可以看到
stroke preview update but you cannot
笔划预览更新 但您不能
paint with a dab alone that would be
只需轻轻一拍就可以作画了
like painting with a clean dry brush you
就像用干干净净的画笔画你
also need media applied to the dab so
还需要将介质应用于DAB 以便
that you can create a stroke on the
您可以在
canvas the types of media you can
画布您可以使用的媒体类型
emulate can vary from oil paint to chalk
模拟可以从油画颜料到粉笔有所不同
to watercolor and just like with a
到水彩画 就像用一个
traditional brush you can load oils or
传统的刷子 你可以装油或
watercolor on the same bristle brush
同一刷子上的水彩画
when you paint with this brush dab the
当你用这个画笔作画时 轻拍
the shape of the bristles Remains the
这些刷毛的形状仍然是
Same but the media used can vary in the
相同 但所使用的媒体在
paint category I'll choose the brush
画笔类别我会选择画笔
called watercolor texture then I'll use
叫水彩纹理 那我就用
the brush tip section of the brush
画笔的画笔尖端部分
Editor to adjust the spacing of this
编辑以调整此文件的间距
brush you can see the stroke preview
笔刷你可以看到笔划预览
updates and real time as I move the
在我移动时更新和实时
slider if I reduce the spacing all the
滑块 如果我缩小所有
way down the dabs merge to become a
往下走 DAB合并成一个
continuous Line This is How many of the
连续线这是有多少
brushes were in cret I'll draw on the
刷子是混凝土的 我会在上面画的
canvas and you can see that it no longer
画布 你可以看到它不再是
resembles individual splatters but if I
类似于个别飞溅 但如果我
make dabs or click with my mouse they
用我的鼠标轻拍或点击
look like splatters again if I increase
如果我增加了 看起来就像飞溅一样
the spacing then you can see that there
间隔 然后你可以看到那里
are more gaps between the dabs and you
Dabs和你之间的差距会更大吗
get more of a dotted line I can also
得到更多的虚线 我也可以
change the media that comes out of the
更换从中取出的介质
brush while keeping the brush shape
在保持画笔形状的同时进行画笔
intact but that requires me to make a
完好无损 但这需要我做一个
custom brush which we will explore how
我们将探讨如何使用自定义画笔
to do later it's as simple as that when
以后做的事情就这么简单 当
you were painting all you were doing is
你在画画 你所做的只是
repeating a dab loaded with media along
重复与介质一起加载的DAB
a
一个
stroke now that you know how a brush
现在你知道刷子是怎么画的了
works let's learn some of the ways you
让我们来了解一下你的一些方法
can customize your stroke properties
可以自定义笔划属性
I'll temporarily use a black background
我将暂时使用黑色背景
so you can see the cursor more easily as
这样您就可以更容易地看到光标
I demonstrate I have the basic five size
我证明我有基本的五码
opacity paintbrush selected and if I
选择了不透明画笔 如果我
want to make the stroke wider or thinner
我想让笔触变宽或变细
I can go to the properties and I could
我可以去酒店 我可以
choose a brush size there I can enter a
选择画笔大小 我可以在那里输入
numeric value or there's a slider that I
数值 或者有一个滑块表示我
can drag to increase or decrease the
可以拖动以增加或减少
brush size if you keep an eye on the
笔刷大小 如果您密切关注
brush tiip preview you can see that it
刷笔尖预览一下就可以看到了
resizes relative to the value you chose
相对于您选择的值调整大小
the popup panel also offers a slider to
弹出式面板还提供了一个滑块
change the brush
换画笔
size the second method for selecting a
调整第二种选择方法的大小
brush size is to choose a diameter that
画笔的大小是选择一个直径
is relative to your canvas size in this
是相对于此中的画布大小
case you're not really concerned about a
如果你不是真的担心
specific brush size you just know that
具体的画笔大小你只知道
you want a big medium or small brush you
你想要一把大、中、小刷子吗？
could use the sliders in the properties
可以使用属性中的滑块
but a faster way to do it is to use a
但更快的方法是使用
keyboard shortcut hold down shift and
键盘快捷键按住Shift和
tap and drag your pen left or right on
点击并向左或向右拖动您的钢笔
the canvas that will create a a circle
画出一个圆圈的画布
that defines the diameter of your brush
它定义了画笔的直径
in most cases the visual CU is fairly
在大多数情况下 视觉CU相当
accurate but some properties like
准确 但有些属性 如
scatter or tilt may cause the brush
散开或倾斜可能会导致刷子
stroke to exceed the radius you defined
笔划超过您定义的半径
for example the texture spray brush far
例如 纹理喷雾笔刷Far
exceeds its cursor I'll return to the
超过它的光标 我将返回到
basic five size opacity brush most of
基本五种大小的不透明度画笔
the time the brush diameter I choose
我选择刷子直径的时间
will be the maximum size of my brush if
将是我的画笔的最大尺寸 如果
I use maximum pen
我用最大笔
pressure now let's say you have a brush
压力现在假设你有一把刷子
you want to be just a little bit larger
你想要稍微大一点
smaller you can press the left or right
更小的 你可以按左边或右边
bracket keys on your keyboard to change
键盘上的方括号按键要更改
the brush size and increments you may be
画笔大小和增量可能是
able to see that the cursor is growing
能够看到光标正在增长
along with the slider movement I can
随着滑块的移动 我可以
even hold the key down this lets me
即使按住这把钥匙也让我
easily fine-tune my brush if you're
轻松微调我的画笔 如果你
drawing tablet has a touch ring you can
绘图板上有一个触摸环 你可以
program it to use the bracket keys to
对其进行编程以使用方括号按键
resize your brush that way as well there
在那里也可以这样调整画笔的大小
are also Arrow buttons in the properties
也是属性中的箭头按钮
bar you can use to resize the brush
可以用来调整画笔大小的栏
here's my preferred method for resizing
以下是我调整大小的首选方法
the brush rather than using the shift
使用笔刷而不是使用Shift
shortcut on your keyboard you can
键盘上的快捷键可以
program one of the buttons on your pen
给你钢笔上的一个按钮编程
to activate shift for example I have the
例如 要激活Shift 我使用
pro pen selected in the walkom tablet
在Walkom平板电脑中选择了Pro笔
properties and in the pen tab I have the
属性 在笔选项卡中 我有
button that's nearest the tip of the pen
离笔尖最近的按钮
set to a modifier which is set to shift
设置为设置为Shift的修改器
the other pen button is set to
另一支笔按钮设置为
rightclick so if I want to resize my
如果我想要调整我的
brush now all I have to do is hold this
现在刷刷我要做的就是拿着这个
button down and drag my pen I can make a
按下按钮 然后拖动我的笔 我可以做一个
large brush a small brush and everything
大刷子 小刷子 什么都有
in
在……里面
between another way to resize your brush
在调整画笔大小的另一种方法之间
is by using pen pressure which we looked
是通过使用我们看到的钢笔压力
at earlier if you're having trouble
早些时候如果你遇到了麻烦
controlling size with pressure you may
用压力控制大小你可能会
need to calibrate your pen pressure in
需要校准您的钢笔压力
your tablet properties I tend to press
我倾向于按下你的平板电脑属性
firmly when I draw so I set it one notch
我画的时候很坚定 所以我把它定了一个档次
toward firm do the opposite if you have
如果你有 对公司做相反的事情
a light
一盏灯
touch now let's look at how to vary the
Touch Now让我们来看看如何改变
opacity of the brushes I'll demonstrate
我将演示画笔的不透明度
on a medium gray canvas so you can see
在一块中灰色的画布上 所以你可以看到
this more easily I will select the
这更容易 我将选择
digital category and I will choose
数码类和我会选择
airbrush soft if I paint with this brush
如果我用这把刷子作画 喷枪会很软
it gradually builds up the opacity based
它会逐渐建立起基于
on how hard you press if you press
关于如果你按下你按下的力度有多大
lightly the paint will be thinner and
轻轻一点 油漆就会变薄
more transparent if you press harder the
如果您更努力地按下
paint will be thicker and more opaque we
我们的油漆会更厚、更不透明
can control the opacity of a brush from
可以控制画笔的不透明度
the properties bar just like with the
属性栏就像使用
brush size we can numerically enter an
笔刷大小 我们可以用数字输入
opacity level let's say 50% and now the
不透明度级别假设为50% 现在
brush will paint at 50% opacity using
画笔将以50%的不透明度绘制 使用
maximum pressure if we set the opacity
设置不透明度时的最大压力
to 2% then the paint is not going to be
到2% 那么油漆就不会
as opaque when we make Strokes and it
当我们做笔触和它的时候是不透明的
will take more effort to build them up
将需要更多的努力来建立它们
to full opacity there's also an opacity
对于完全不透明 还有一种不透明
slider that we can drag or click on
我们可以拖动或单击的滑块
another way to change the opacity is to
更改不透明度的另一种方法是
use the keyboard shortcuts of I and O
使用I和O的键盘快捷键
this will modify the opacity in 10%
这将修改10%的不透明度
increments you can even change the
增量您甚至可以更改
opacity with a slider in the pop-up
弹出窗口中带有滑块的不透明度
panel typically I build up opacity
面板通常会增加不透明度
gradually using overlapping Strokes so I
逐渐使用重叠笔画 这样我
don't usually change the opacity setting
通常不更改不透明度设置
unless I find that a brush is a bit too
除非我觉得画笔太过
strong or a bit too to
强壮或有点太强了
week those were some of the basics of
周 这些是一些基本的
working with brushes in the next lesson
在下一课中使用画笔
we will be exploring some of the
我们将探索一些
essential functions and cre such as
基本功能和cre 例如
choosing color erasing sampling color
选择颜色擦除采样颜色
and saving
和储蓄
artwork
艺术品